Translate by Lavigkaye
翻译: Lavigkaye
各位 请安静
Everyone, please.
请注意
Please.
很遗憾我有责任要在这里
It's my unfortunate responsibility
告诉大家一个可怕的消息
to share with you some terrible news.
似乎就在上周末
It seems that over the weekend
我们的同学玛丽娜·米尔斯自杀了
a fellow student Marina Mills committed suicide.
传闻她将自杀过程用摄像头拍下来是吗?
Is it true that she filmed it on her webcam?
你的同班同学死了 而你就只关心
one of your classmates died and all you care about
是否能够看得到?
is whether you can see it?
似乎今天早上的确有一段影片
Apparently, there was a video uploaded
被上传到学校网站里
to the university website this morning.
你们当中有些同学在学校将影片删除前
Some of you were crafty enough to grab it
就已经很快将影片下载了
before we could take it down.
我劝你们不要 不要去看
I urge you not to, to watch it.
任何人被发现将影片分享出去会立即被停课
Anyone caught sharing it will be suspended, period.
无任何求情理由
no discussion.
你们当中有没有那些是玛丽娜的朋友?
were any of you friends with Marina?
或者有任何信息可以说明这埸悲剧?
Or have any info that can shed light on this tragedy?
如果有 请在下课后来找我
If so, see me after class.
Translate by Lavigkaye
翻译: Lavigkaye
朋友请求
两周之前
丽芙 这影片太有趣了!
Liv, this video is so cute.
- 吓不到我的 - 对啊 对啊
- So not scary. - Yeah, right.
这影片非常好
This is so good.
罗拉·伍德森
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿 - 你好啊
- Hey. - Hello.
有人昨晚没有回家呢
Someone didn't come home last night.
对啊 又没回家
Yeah, again.
所以现在你们两个是夫妻还是什么了?
So are you guys, like, monogamous now or what?
丽芙 那不是一个粗口 天啊
Liv, it's not a dirty word. Jesus.
好明显 我知道 我只是妒忌 被人抛弃
I know. Clearly, I'm just jealous, you know, being dumped.
你没有被人抛弃 你只认识他一天
You were not dumped. You knew him for one day.
那是个美好的一天
It was an amazing day.
嗯 好 很好 喜欢吗 嗯
Hmm. Yeah. Yeah, like that? Yeah.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
- 嗯 我明白 - 真疯狂
- Hmm. I know. - This is crazy.
那你现在跟谁交往中吗?
So you're in a, in a relationship?
- 噢 又来了! - 不 无关系 真的无关系
- Oh, here we go. - No, it's super cool. Really.
我只是 只是很喜欢你上传的所有
I just, you know, love all these precious little updates
你和冲浪医生的珍贵小更新
about you and Dr. surfboard.
- 对你很好 - 噢 闭嘴吧
- Good for you. - Oh, shut up.
另一种说法是关于网络成瘾症
Another argument that Internet addiction disorder
并不属于精神疾病类
doesn't belong in the dsm
没有经常性的症状或异常
is that it's frequently symptomatic of other disorders.
如抑郁 焦虑或创伤
depression, anxiety, trauma.
通常 这是让我们逃离现实的方法
often, it's an escape from things we don't wanna deal with.
让我们远离日常生活中的事 差远了
From our everyday lives to things far, far worse.
虽然最常见的疾病可能只是
Though the most common disorder might just be
令我们的双手过度疲劳
that we have too much time on our hands.
矜持点
Play it cool.
等几天先
Wait a few days.
他已经知道我一点都不矜持
He already knows I'm not cool.
我想我们班上就已经有些
I think we might have an excellent example
很好的网络成瘾症例子
of Internet addiction disorder right here in class.
除了伍德森小姐和马西森小姐之外
Beside from miss woodson and miss mathison
这里有没有其他人出现任何症状?
does anyone else here experience symptoms?
- 看看这张 - 我很喜欢 我喜欢这张
- look at that. - I love it. I like that.
- 这张拍得真好 - 噢 我真的很喜欢这个滤镜
- That's a nice one. - Oh, I really like that filter.
- 我可以教你怎样做 - 看看高比 天啊
- I can show you how to do it. - Look at Kobe. Jesus.
他什么时候才放得下你?
when's he gonna get over you?
他真是一个变态
he's such a creeper.
- 他不是个变态 - 噢
- he is not a creeper! - Oh.
那是谁?
Who's that?
我班上的一个女孩
A girl in my class.
零个朋友 怎么做到的 超级怪异?
Zero friends. How's that not, like, super weird?
可能她刚刚才开始玩呢
maybe she just started her profile or something.
她看起来像个十二岁的小孩
is she like 12 years old?
哈 我觉得她很有才华
Ha. I think she's really talented.
我喜欢
I like it.
你喜欢她在课堂上撕掉她自己的头发?
You like it when she rips her hair out during class?
噢 别这样
Oh, come on.
我今天真的看到她拔走自己的眼睫毛
i literally saw her pull an eyelash out today.
呃 这是种强迫行为 叫作拔毛癖
uh, it's a condition. It's called trichotillomania.
如果你间中打开一次教科书看看
You would know all about it if you crack open a textbook
你就会知道了有关它的一切
every once in a while.
- 噢! - 噢 随便了
- Owned! - Oh, whatever.
事实上我下年准备转另一个科目
I'm actually changing majors next year.
噢 是吗 那再下一年呢?
Oh, yeah, and the year after that?
- 噢 又一击! - 好了
- Owned! Twofer. - Come on.
随便了!
Whatever.
噢 你在煮什么?
Oh, what are you making?
是不是咖哩海鲜? 噢 真好
is that seafood curry? Oh, it's good.
什么? 咖哩海鲜? 不 这是...
what? Seafood curry. No, this is..
我的爸爸是一名精神科医生
well, my dad was a psychiatrist
所以 我想跟随他去当一名精神科医生
so I guess I, you know, wanna follow in his footsteps.
这很好啊
That's nice.
你读这科目是为了拿学分还是...
Are you doing it for credit or you just..
你真的想去做?
You really wanna do it?
我不肯定 我刚刚才转到这里
I'm not sure. I just transferred.
- 我 我还未认识任何人 - 你现在认识我了
- I-i don't know anyone yet. - Well, now you know me.
你住在宿舍吗?
Are you in the dorms?
我朋友和我租了间公寓来住
My friends and I, we just got an apartment.
这感觉很好 但肯定的是
It's amazing, but we're definitely
我们一样事情都没有做好
not getting any work done.
- 太多的朋友 - 就是啊
- Too many friends. - Exactly.
我们晚点再见
I'll see you around campus.
再见 罗拉
Bye, Laura.
我以为医科生也有功课呢
I thought med students had homework.
- 你想谈一会吗? - 呃 我在学习啊
- You wanted to talk. - Well, I'm studying.
网络成瘾症
Internet addiction disorder.
而你就是你自己的个案研究对象吗?
And you're your own case study.
完全正确
Exactly.
这女孩有什么问题?
What's the deal with this girl?
我不知道 我觉得她有点孤单
I don't know. I think she's lonely.
她会成为你的朋友还是你第一位的精神病人?
Is she gonna be your friend or your first mental patient?
她会成为我的第二位精神病人
She'll be my second mental patient.
她将我全部放上网的东西都看了
She's going through every post I've ever made in my life.
哇 她真疯狂
wow. She's crazy.
看 看看她刚刚发给我的东西
Look, look what she just sent me.
什么 我又要看
What, I wanna see.
噢! 啊!
Oh. Uh.
噢 你们两个要永远幸福快乐的一起生活了
Oh, you guys are gonna live happily ever after together.
- 我的天啊 - 真甜蜜
- Oh, my god. - How nice.
- 她究竟是什么人啊? - 我不知道
- Who is this person? - I don't know.
喂 拉下去 我想看看她的贴文
Dude, scroll down. I wanna see her timeline.
继续
Further.
further.
哇
whoa.
天啊
Jesus.
难怪她会令你作恶梦
no wonder this girl's giving you nightmares.
关了它
close it.
- 噢 - 我的天啊!
- Oh. - Oh, my god.
罗拉 这个女孩有问题
Laura, this girl isn't right.
为什么你要和她玩?
Why are you hanging out with her?
我只是想表示友好
I was just trying to be nice.
天啊 我简直不能相信你邀请了她参加你的生日
God! I can't believe you invited her to your birthday.
不 不 不 不 我没有邀请她
No, no, no, no. I didn't invite her.
她自己想来 我要怎样说呢?
She invited herself. What was I supposed to say?
嗯 你可以说点 例如 妈的 不可以
Um, how about something like, fuck, no?
嗯 换着我就会这样说
Yeah, that sounds about right to me.
你不可以这样对人说的
You can't say that to someone.
- 噢 对啊 就是这样 你可以这样说
- Oh, yeah. It goes like this. - Yes, you can.
就好像这样 嘿 罗拉 我可以参加你的生日吗?
It goes like this. "Hey, Laura, can I come to your birthday?"
- 妈的 不可以 - 就是这样
- Fuck, no! - There you go.
终于接听了 罗拉 生日快乐
Laura, finally. Happy birthday.
- 你看起来真美 - 谢谢你 玛丽娜
- You look so pretty. - Thanks, Marina.
- 你有收到我的讯息吗? - 嗯 我怎会错过了
- You get my messages? - Yeah, how can I miss them?
你在生我的气吗? 我有做错了什么吗?
Are you mad at me? Did I do something wrong?
不 我没有生你的气 我只是...
No, I'm not mad at you, I'm just..
我们明天在班上再见好吗?
I'll see you in class tomorrow, okay?
但今晚呢?
But what about tonight?
你不和你的朋友去庆祝吗?
Aren't you celebrating with your friends?
呃 今晚只是我和泰勒
Uh, it's just Tyler and I tonight.
我们会去晚餐 所以...
We're going out to dinner, so..
只有我们两个
Just the two of us.
但你根本不熟悉她
But you barely know her.
今天晚上不是只有你和你的朋友吗?
isn't tonight just you and your friends?
我明 我明
I know, I know.
我只是觉得 我不想讨厌地说谎
I just feel, you know, icky lying about it.
嗯 你对我来说一点都不讨厌
Well, you don't look very icky to me.
去吧
Go ahead.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 妈咪
Hi, mom.
- 嘿 生日快乐 - 嗨
- Hey, happy birthday. - Hi.
我一直在灌你妈咪喝酒
I've been trying to get your mom as drunk as possible.
你真是一个很帅的小子
You actually knew a beautiful guy
你要和我一起喝酒 那我们就可以...
you need to get drunk with me, so we know..
对啊 完全从表面上说中了他们 所以他们开始好评了
Yeah, it's literally hurt 'em so they started to praise it.
而最后一个原因 无论什么
And the last reason, no matter what
你永远都会给我一些很疯狂
that you'll always find some crazy way
的方法来让我觉得更好
to make me feel better.
真肉麻
Aww.
等等 等等 给我的小女孩
wait, wait, wait, to my little green bean
你每日都令我感到自豪
who makes me so proud every day
还有你父亲也一样 每一秒都在为你感到自豪
and who made her father so proud every single second.
噢 妈咪
Oh, mom.
好了 轮到我了
Alright, I'm getting in.
让我也加入这充满爱的小船
I'm bumping in this little love boat.
不 我要说了 我要说了 好吗?
No, I'm going, I'm going, okay?
呃 这 这是敬我们大家的 一个非常美好的夜晚
Uh, this is, this is to us. A-a wonderful evening.
还有敬未来 未来会更好 更成功
To, to the future, to success.
还有你闭嘴 你这个醉酒鬼
and you shut up, you drunk floozy.
还有这个 这个只是给你的
And then this is also to, to just to you.
生日快乐
A happy birthday.
多谢大家
Thanks you, guys.
- 嘿 罗拉 你好吗? - 嘿 你好吗?
- Hey, Laura. How are you doing? - Hey, how are you?
- 我很好 - 那就好了
- I'm good. - That's good.
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
玛丽娜 你在 你在说什么啊?
Marina, what are, what are you talking about?
我昨晚看到你们了 你的生日晚餐
I saw you with everyone. Your birthday dinner.
- 我看到了 - 玛丽娜 我很抱歉
- I saw it. - Marina, I'm sorry.
我 我不是有心欺骗你的
I, I didn't mean to hurt your feelings.
我们可以晚点再说吗?
Can we talk about this later, okay?
我有个礼物给你 我准备了两个星期了
I had a present for you. I worked on it for two weeks.
两个星期? 你才刚刚认识我两个星期呢
Two weeks? You've barely known me for two weeks.
你这该死的骗子 你就像其他人一样!
You fucking liar, you're just like everyone else!
你为什么要接受我的好友请求?
Why did you accept my friend request?
- 你不用一定要接受的 - 快点放开我啊!
- You didn't have to do that! - Get the fuck off me!
你知道孤独是什么的感觉吗?
Do you have any idea what it feels to be alone?
- 完完全全的孤独 - 放开我 你这怪胎!
- Completely alone.. - Get off me, you freak!
罗拉 你没有做错什么
Laura, you didn't do anything wrong.
那女生根本就有问题
This chick is just damaged.
泰勒 你当时不在那里
You weren't there, Tyler.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
亲爱的 我真的很抱歉
Baby, I'm really sorry.
但我真的要回去继续解剖死人了
I gotta get back to cutting up dead people.
好吧
okay.
她想跟我视像通话 我应该怎么做?
She's tryin' to face-chat me. What do I do?
不要接听! 我说真的!
Don't take the call. Seriously.
好吧 我晚点再跟你说
Fine, alright. I'll talk to you later.
好的 再见
Okay. Bye.
丽芙?
Liv?
呃?
Hmm.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
快回去睡觉吧
Go to bed.
下课后我再告诉你整件事...
let me after class to tell you a story..
请安静 各位 请注意
Please. Everyone, please.
很遗憾我有责任要在这里
it's my unfortunate responsibility
告诉大家一个可怕的消息
to share with you some terrible news.
似乎就在上周末我们的同学
It seems that over the weekend your fellow student
玛丽娜·米尔斯自杀了
Marina Mills committed suicide.
你还好吗?
How'd it go?
无事
Fine.
我刚刚跟学校说了她近乎
I just told them she was stalking me.
疯狂地缠绕我的事
Kind of like crazy.
嘿 别将这件事怪责自己
Hey, don't beat yourself up about it.
那个女孩完全是个怪胎
That girl was completely nuts.
她只是需要人帮助去度过
She needed help though.
嗯 非常严重的帮助
Yeah, like serious help.
在二年级时绝不能错过心理学课
Never miss sophomore in psych 201.
向好的一面想
Look on the bright side.
也许我们班可以为她举行一个葬礼
might be able to get out of class for the funeral.
不 不 不 没有葬礼 根本没有尸体
No-no-no, there's not gonna be a funeral. There's no body.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
呃 警方今天早上来过我的宿舍
Uh, um, cops were at my dorm this morning
他们不知道她在那里自杀 至少不在宿舍里
and, and they don't know where she did it, but it wasn't there.
呃 事实上她自从上周末以来就一直没有用过她的房卡
Uh, actually, she hasn't swiped her keycard since last weekend.
而这点不是最奇怪的地方 最令我感到奇怪的是
and that's not what freaks me out, what freaks me out
警方根本不知道这个女孩的背景
is that they don't know who this girl even was.
她 呃 联络数据 她的社保号码
Her, uh, contact info, her social security
在整个学校的数据库中被删除
it's all been deleted from the school database.
警方连她的名字玛丽娜·米尔斯是否她的真名也不知道
They don't even think that Marina mills was her real name.
呃 你说真的吗?
uh, are you serious?
- 我的天啊 - 怎么了?
- Oh, my god. - What's going on?
为什么你要看这个?
Why are you watching this?
- 是谁传送这鬼东西给你的? - 她
- Who sent you this crap? - She did.
- 她死了 - 我知道
- she's dead. - I know.
好了 你会有六十分钟的时间
Again, you'll have 60 minutes.
这是一个真实的案例研究 一个具有挑战性的
This is an actual case study. A challenging one.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
天啊
God.
这是那段影片吗?
Is that the video?
我以为你说在你的讯息里 你发布了?
I thought you said it was in your messages. You posted it?
不 不 有人发布了 不是我
No, no, someone did. I didn't.
而且标签了我所有的朋友
And they tagged all my friends.
伍德森小姐 不要使用手提电脑
Laptops away, miss woodson.
为什么他们会以为是我做的 我 我绝对不会这样做的
Why would they think I did that? I would, I would never do that.
你有没有尝试换密码?
Did you try changing your password?
有 有啊 我尝试了一切
Yes, yes, I've tried everything.
她不断会回到我的好友清单中
She's even back in my friend's list.
解除那个死婊子的好友关系
Unfriend that dead bitch.
我解除不了
I can't.
所以伍德森小姐 根据你说的情况
So according to you, miss woodson, this video
这影片今天早上就神奇地出现在你的主页上?
just magically appeared on your timeline this morning?
- 我说得正确吗? - 为什么我要发出去?
- Do I have that right? - Why would I do this?
一定是有某种原因令那个女孩会烧掉你的画像
There must be some reason this girl burned that picture of you.
听着 罗拉 我们知道你是一个好学生
Look, Laura, we know that you're a great student
但有很多学生都投诉你骚扰玛丽娜
but multiple students reported you harassing Marina.
不! 她才是那个骚扰我的人
No, she was the one harassing me.
她沉迷着我
She was obsessed with me.
罗拉 没有人说玛丽娜的死
Laura, no one's saying it's your fault
是你的错
that Marina took her life.
我们只是在追查每一件事
We're looking into everything.
但罗拉 现在如果你无法删除那段影片的话
But in the meantime, Laura, if you can't delete that video
你就要将你整个账号删除
you're gonna have to delete your profile.
嘿 还有一件事
hey, one more thing.
你有任何头绪知道那个女孩自焚的地方吗?
Any idea where this girl might have torched herself?
没有
No.
不 你没有听明白我说什么 我无法删除那段影片
No, you're not listening to me. I can't delete this video.
我连我的账号也无法删除
I can't even delete my account.
就像我说的一样 这里不是客户中心
Like I said, this isn't a call center.
好吧 那为什么我不能解除和一个死去的女孩的好友关系?
okay, well, what about that dead girl I can't unfriend?
你对此能做些什么呢？
Can you do something about that?
女士 我没有见到任何那女孩的账号
Ma'am, I'm not seeing this profile.
什么? 我刚刚才见到!
what? I just saw it.
还有没有其他人可以跟我说?
Is there anyone else i can speak to?
我很抱歉他们只会跟你说同样的话
I'm afraid they'll just tell you the same thing.
接下来怎么办?
what's next?
高比 我知道你就在这里 我可以听到你在玩游戏
Kobe, I know you're in there. I can hear your stupid game.
你发布了段很好的影片呢
That was a nice video you posted.
嗯 这就是我来的原因
Yeah, that's what I'm here about.
哇
Wow.
你是她唯一的朋友 真够特别啊
You're her only friend. How special is that?
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
天啊 有人还在上传些东西
Christ, someone's still uploading things.
这 这太正了!
That, that's intense.
我太他妈的喜欢了!
I fucking love it.
噢 对了
Oh, alright.
好了 让我们来看看后台的情况
Okay, let's take a little peek behind the curtains.
怎么了?
What?
你一点都不知道这有多奇怪 对吧
you have no idea how crazy that is, do you?
好了 看看这个
Okay. Look at that.
看 这 这些是正常的代码
Look, that, that is what code normally looks like.
不是这种
not this.
这 这东西连复制也不能 这 这根本不是代码
I-i can't even copy this. This isn't, this isn't code.
那 这是什么?
Well, w-what is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
等等 你可以拉回上去吗
Wait, wait. Can you go back?
不要再看那个女孩的主页了
Just stop looking at that girl's profile.
不要再想起她了
stop thinking about her.
她自杀了 告一段落 故事完结
she killed herself. End of story.
她在自己的手提电脑前点燃自己然后上吊自杀
She burned and hung herself in front of her laptop.
谁会这样做啊?
Who does that?
现在要去管这事吗?
is this gonna be a thing now?
你去高比的宿舍和他一起做什么了
You and Kobe hanging out in his dorm room.
你现在真的在想那些事吗?
Is that really what you're thinking about right now?
嗯 我在想我们两个
Yeah, I'm thinking about us.
那又有什么问题?
What's wrong with that?
他只是个朋友 你知道的
He's just a friend, you know that.
他是这样想的吗?
Does he?
如果你不上网 他们就骚扰不了你
It's called cyberstalking for a reason.
这就是叫作所谓的网络跟踪的原因
they can't bother you if you're not online.
呃 嗯 给我买一些
Uh, yeah. Get me some of those
呃 朱古力坚果酥一样的东西
uh, chocolate macadamia crisp thingies.
不 不是 呃 就像 朱古力薯片
no, they're not, uh, like, chocolate potato chips.
它们就像曲奇一样
they're like cookies.
呃 类似饼干
like, uh, crackers, kind of.
就问那个人吧 我经常都会去那里
just ask the guy there. I go there all the time.
白白肥肥的孩子很爱朱古力
The white chubby kid who loves chocolate.
宝贝 你不是小孩了 天啊 你真挑剔
Babe, you're not chubby. You're very fussy. My god!
我不是挑剔 只是朱古力
I'm not being fussy, I'm on my period
会令我感觉良好
and chocolate makes me feel better.
伊莎贝尔?
Isabel?
听到吗?
Hello?
该死的!
Shit.
查得?
Chad?
有人吗?
Hello?
高比?
Kobe?
老友啊 这不有趣!
You guys, this isn't funny.
真的!
Seriously.
老友?
Guys?
高比 出来吧 好友
Kobes, come on, man.
什么鬼啊?
What the hell?
什...
What..
什么鬼东西来的!
What the fuck.
不! 不! 不! 不! 不!
No, no, no, no, no.
噢!
oh.
不!
No!
不要啊!
停下!
No!
不要!
no!
不要啊!
No!
好了 她现在勉强可以说话了
Okay, so she's barely talking right now.
他们要她在这里留院观察 也可能要住一段时间
They're gonna her overnight. Maybe longer.
如果你们想的话可以去看她
You can see her if you want.
听着 我不太熟悉古斯塔沃
Listen, I didn't know Gustavo that well.
他是不是吸了毒?
Was he on something?
没有
No.
我看了验尸报告 简直疯狂
I saw the medical report. It is insane.
拜托 请你走吧
Please, just leave.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
这全是她的错
this is all her fault.
罗拉 她现在不清醒
She's not herself, Laura.
不! 那个不是古斯
No, Gus wasn't himself.
他之前开始发恶梦
He was having nightmares.
我也一样
so am I.
你吓到我们了 你在说什么啊?
You're scaring us, is. What are you talking about?
罗拉知道的
Laura knows!
她很清楚
She knows.
感觉一切都很虚假
It doesn't feel real.
答应我你今天不会去看那女孩的主页
Promise me you won't look at that girl's profile today.
你令到自己快疯了
You're driving yourself crazy.
删除你的账号
Delete your account.
我说真的
Seriously.
你想伊莎贝尔也看到吗?
You want Isabel to see that?
丽芙你知道的 我删除不了
Liv, you know I can't.
我不理要如何 快删了它!
I don't care how. Just do it.
妈的
Fuck.
有很多学生给了我压力
Even if it's not you behind these posts
即使这些贴文不是由你本人发的
I'm getting a lot of pressure from the students.
这些贴文一直继续出现 我别无选择
As long as the posts are up, i have no choice
只好中止你余下的学期 暂时休学
but to suspend you for the rest of the semester.
妈 其实你不需要经常打给我的
Mom, you don't always have to call me on facetime, you know.
- 你为什么不打给我? - 对不起
- Why didn't you call me? - I'm sorry.
我 我只是不想你担心 好吗?
I, I didn't want you to worry, okay?
我会来接你 我想你回家
I'm coming to pick you up. I want you home.
不 听着 我保证我晚点再打给你 好吗?
No. Look, look, I'll call you later. I promise, okay?
看看这个
Look at that.
什么鬼啊!
What the hell.
嗯 她在他死之前跟他做了好友
Yeah, she friended him right before he died.
还有些事情
There's something else.
- 天啊 高比 我不... - 我不是要你去看
- Jesus, Kobe, I don't-- - I don't want you to watch it.
我希望你听一下
I want you to listen.
那是什么?
What is that?
我不知道 我想是黑蜂的声音
I don't know. I think it's wasps.
她整个主页都是些黑蜂
She's got black wasps all over her profile.
我做了些搜查 呃
I did some research, and, um'
有些人将黑蜂与邪恶联系在一起
some people associated them with evil.
他们说黑蜂出现在女巫居住的地方附近
they say they appeared wherever witches lived.
它们 跟随着女巫 在她们身边保护她们
They, like, follow them around and protect them.
天啊
Jesus.
这个女孩究竟是谁?
Who is this girl?
你觉得你可以让我们进去她的房间吗?
Do you think you could get us into her room?
好了 来吧
Come on, now.
她不太时尚对吗?
Not much into fashion, was she?
你知不知道你要找些什么?
Do you even know what you're looking for?
呃 任何东西
Well, just anything.
噢 嘿 嘿 看看 看看这个
Oh, hey, hey. Look, look, look.
- 这是她 - 那这两个又是谁?
- That's her. - And who are these two?
你可以找到这间是什么学校吗?
can you find what school this is?
如果网上有数据的话当然可以
If it's ever been online, yeah.
你是否就是那个打电话来的年轻女孩?
Are you the young lady who called?
玛丽娜的朋友?
Marina's friend?
对
Yes.
你跟她有多熟悉?
How close did you say you were again?
我只是刚开始认识她...
I was just getting to know her when she..
我连她的真名也不知道
I didn't even know her real name.
妮蒂法 玛丽娜·妮蒂法
Nedifar, Marina Nedifar.
你知道她的父母发生什么事吗?
Do you know what happened to her parents?
我对那些一无所知
I wouldn't know anything about that.
她是作为一个病人来到我们这里
She came to us as a ward of the state.
可怜的小女孩 她在这里有过很痛苦的经历
Poor girl, she had such a rough go of things here.
她总是很敏感 一直都是一个人
She was always very sensitive. Always alone.
投入她自己的幻想世界中
Fleeing into her little fantasy worlds.
她还在网上找到了一些黑暗的东西
And she found some dark corners online.
一些小孩不应该去看的东西
Things no child should see.
有时候她就只盯着计算机几个小时
Sometimes she would just stare at the computer for hours.
银幕上什么都没有
Nothing on the screen at all.
只有她在黑暗中倒影
Just her own reflection in the darkness.
其他小孩子都很害怕她
The kids became terrified of her.
他们说她令他们作恶梦
They said she gave them nightmares.
妈的
Fuck!
天啊
Jesus.
那两个在相片中的男孩
The two boys in the photo
他们都被发现死在 Saddle Mills 附近
they were found dead near saddle mills
面部都是残缺不全
with their faces mutilated.
他们都是被一堆黑蜂袭击致死
They were swarmed by black wasps.
什么?
What?
泰勒 我知道这可能会令你惹上麻烦
Tyler, I know you could get in trouble for this
但 拜托 你能否
but please, can you
能否在什么地方可以找到她的记录?
can you access her records somehow?
例如家庭联络或者最后的地址?
Like a family contact or the last address?
任何东西?
Something?
我们连她姓什么都不知道
we don't even know her last name.
妮蒂法
Nedifar.
玛丽娜·妮蒂法
Marina Nedifar.
罗拉?
Laura?
有人吗?
Hello?
有谁在吗?
Is anybody here?
有人吗?
Hello?
这不是真的 这不是真的
This is not real. This is not real.
这不是真的
This is not real.
不! 这不是真的!
No. This is not real.
这不是真的
This is not real!
伍德森小姐
Miss Woodson.
她在切开自己喉咙之前把自己的头发都撕掉了
she rips out on her own hair before she slits her throat.
这是我当警察二十五年来
Now I've been on this job 25 years
第一次遇上的事情
and that's a first for me.
是不是有一些我们不知道的低劣新毒品出现了?
There's some shitty new drug we don't know about?
我从来都没有碰过那些东西
I never took anything.
我想知道的是 你是在那里找到那段
What I wanna know is, where you got the elevator footage
升降机影片来发布?
that you posted.
我最后说多一次 我没有发布过任何这些东西
For the last time, I'm not posting any of this.
嗯 好消息是我们从你的网络地址上
Well, the good news for you is we can't link
没有找到任何和那些影片有关连
your ip address to any of these videos.
事实上我们根本找不到任何网络地址
We couldn't find any address at all
这根本就说不通
which doesn't make any sense.
除非你非常熟悉我们的网络部门
Unless you are familiar with our it department.
这一切都是那个女孩做的
It all has to do with this girl.
伍德森小姐 你认识很多死人呢
You really know a lot of dead people, Miss Woodson.
这不是真的...
This is not real..
罗拉 我不认为这是一个自杀行为
I don't think this was a suicide, Laura.
我认为这是一种仪式
I think it was a ritual.
呃 这些 你在这里看到的
Um, that, what you're lookin' at here
这些 这些叫作黑镜
these are, these are black mirrors.
他们在千百年前就已经被用作超自然用途
They've been used in the occult for thousands of years.
他们说 如果你 如果你直视着它
and they say that if you, if you stare into it
你就可以和另一边沟通
you can communicate with some other sides.
这 这叫作占卜
It's, it's, it's called scrying.
但有时这些女巫 如果她们被猎杀
but sometimes these witches, if they were being hunted
而她们没有其他任何方法可以做
if they didn't have any other, any other way out
她们就会站在黑镜前
they would hang and burn themselves
点燃自己然后上吊自杀 之后就变成其他东西
in front of a black mirror and become something else.
你想怎么叫都可以 邪灵
Call it whatever you want. An evil spirit.
呃 魔鬼
Um, a, a demon.
重点是 这是她们用来报复人们的方法
Point is, it's how they got revenge on people.
呃 缠绕他们 困扰他们
uh, possessing them and-and haunting them
还有杀死他们
and killing them.
那他们如何阻止?
How'd they ever stop it?
网上说他们要找到那块原本的镜子
It says they had to find the original mirror.
那一块被她们站在面前点燃自己然后上吊的黑镜 把它毁灭
The one they burned themselves in front of, destroy it.
你指是她的手提电脑?
You mean her laptop?
那就是她的黑镜
It was her black mirror.
我们需要找到她究竟在那里进行自杀
We need to find out where she killed herself.
噢 噢 我的天啊!
oh. Oh, my god.
我想 我想 这里一定隐藏着些什么
I mean, there, there has to be something here.
你明的 一些可以帮到我们的东西
You know, something that can help us.
我想我要回家了
I think I'm going home.
我承受不了这些事
I can't handle this.
我对这一切感到很抱歉
I'm so sorry for everything.
- 请不要走 - 对不起
- Please, don't go. - I'm sorry.
我不能
I can't.
你来迟了
You're late.
为什么每个人都这样说你?
Why is everyone talking about you?
你对那个女孩做了什么?
What have you done to this girl?
我没有对她做过什么!
I haven't done anything to her.
她就一直缠绕着我
She just attached herself to me.
而现在每个人都认为...
And now everyone thinks that..
拜托 宝贝 我想你回家 你跟我回家吧
Please, I want you home, baby. You're coming home with me.
不能 我不能 我要留在这里 弄清整件事
Well, I can't. I can't. I have to stay and figure it out.
弄清什么?
Figure what out?
...遭受重伤
...suffered serious injuries.
警方已将嫌疑人扣押
Police have the suspect in custody
直到他们完成整个调查之前
but they're not releasing any information
他们不会发布任何嫌疑人的信息
until they complete their investigation.
Moore's Grove
Moore's Grove.
那是一个废弃的农场镇 约两个小时的路程
it's a deserted farm town about two hours away.
那里有个奇怪社团在二十年前
There was a fire there 20 years ago
发生了一埸大火
at some weird commune.
玛丽娜的母亲 埃达·妮蒂法 就住在那里
Marina's mother, Ada nedifar, lived there
直到某人将那个地方烧清光
until somebody burnt the whole place down.
什么?
what?
他们努力维持着她的性命...
They kept some husk of her body alive...
...一直到玛丽娜出生
...until Marina was delivered.
她自己一个在子宫里度过了数个月
She was alone in the womb for months.
天啊 她一直都是孤独一个
Jesus, she was always alone.
你觉得那里会是她自杀的地方吗?
You think this is where she went to kill herself?
我的意思是 这是我们唯一的线索
I mean, it's the only lead we have.
她的主页发生了什么? 那是什么?
What going on with her profile? What's that on there?
嘿 我是奥利维亚 留下你的讯息
Hey, it's Olivia. Leave me a ping.
不对路 可能有事发生了
something's wrong, something's wrong.
就停在那里!
Stop right here.
停在那里 让我下车!
Stop right here and let me out.
我的天啊!
Oh, my god.
奥利维亚
Olivia.
下车 赶快下车救她
get out, get out and help her.
- 救她啊 - 救我
- Help her. - Save me.
- 多谢你医生 - 嗯
- Thank you so much, doctor. - Yeah.
她情况稳定
she's stable.
她很有可能会挺过来
She might actually make it through this.
即使她挺过来...
Even if she does..
...玛丽娜也不会停手
...Marina's never gonna stop.
真该死!
Shit.
拜托你 留 留在这里陪丽芙
Just, just stay here. Stay with Liv, please.
不要让她自己单独一个人
Don't let her be alone.
你 你要去那里?
W-where are you going?
哇 有人过了一个很不幸的一天呢
Whoa! Someone had a rough day.
如果那里还有人住的话怎么办? 我的意思是...
What happens if there's still people living here? I mean..
那里现在变成怎样了?
What is this place now?
我不知道
I don't know.
不管怎样 我都要找到那部手提电脑
No matter what, I'm finding that laptop
然后将它狠狠地打烂!
and I'm gonna fuckin' smash it.
- 高比 - 嗯
- Kobe. - Yeah.
多谢你陪我去
Thanks for coming with me.
谁说我是为了你而去的?
Who says I'm doing it for you?
你去了什么鬼地方啊?
Where the hell are you?
那些警察不断地问我各种问题
the cops are asking me a million questions.
对不起 我 我正在去 Moore's Grove
I'm, I'm going to Moore's Grove. I'm sorry.
不要自己一个人去那里啊!
Don't go there alone.
我 我不是自己一个人 我 我跟高比在一起
I, I'm not alone. I'm, I'm with Kobe.
我现在就过去找你
I'm coming to meet you.
那 她在那里?
So, where is she?
我不知道 讯号不好
I don't know, man. Bad reception.
- 嗯 - 好吧 继续尝试
- Yeah. - Alright, keep trying.
真该死!
Shit.
- 真好啊 - 嗯
- Charming. - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
该死的! 这里没有讯号
Shit, there's no service.
你为什么对这件事这么紧张 你会没事的
What are you so fucking nervous about? You're gonna be fine.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你说过她想令你孤单一个人
You said she wants to make you lonely.
如果是真的话 那你就是我们当中唯一一个安全的
If that's true, then you are the only one that's safe.
噢 嘿 亲爱的
Oh, hey, sweetheart.
我说不好 不要去中国
I said no. No Chinese for you.
不 不要 不 我说不要去中国
N-no, no, no, i-i said no Chinese.
不要去中国 我说...
No Chinese, I said..
当然 嗯 不 好吧 我的意思是我们 我们可以去中国
Sure, yeah, no, I mean, we-we could have Chinese, alright.
只是...只是...
From down.. No down at the one by the..
嗯 我晚点再联络你
Yeah, I'll call you back.
拜托 不要 我不想死 拜托 求求你
Please, no. I don't wanna die. Please, please.
噢 我的天啊!
Oh, my god.
你不是吧?
You really?
罗拉
Laura.
- 高比 - 什么?
- Kobe. - What?
她不在这里
She's not here.
你有没有检查过地下室?
Did you check the basement?
什么地下室?
What basement?
高比
Kobe.
有什么问题了?
what's wrong?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
如果你死了她就不能令到你孤独了
She can't make you lonely if you're dead.
罗拉
Laura!
Laura.
嘿 我是罗拉 留下讯息吧
Hey, it's Laura. Leave a message.
你说不知道她在那里是什么意思?
what do you mean you don't know where she is?
那里发生了什么事?
What happened back there?
嘿 你他妈的听不听到我在跟你说话?
Hey, don't you know I'm fucking talking to you?
发生什么事了?
What happened?
听着 如果你伤害了她 我肯定会杀了你
Listen to me, if you touch her, I'll fucking kill you.
- 她究竟在那里? - 她肯定没有事的
- Now where the hell is she? - She is absolutely fine.
而我们都死定了
We are completely fucked.
她就是个宝贝
She's just peachy.
泰勒
Tyler.
罗拉? 感谢上天 我以为你发生了什么事了
Laura, thank god. I thought something happened to you.
我 我发个地址给你
I-i just texted you an address.
罗拉 我 我 我听不清你在说什么
Laura, i-i cant, i can't hear you.
你的讯号很差
You're breaking up.
泰勒
Tyler.
你确定你不需要我带去医院吗?
Are you sure you don't want me to take you to a hospital?
带我去工厂那里
take me to the factory.
你认为我们可以打败这东西吗?
So you think we can beat this, don't you?
你闭嘴啊!
Shut up, man.
说真的
Seriously.
你根本不清楚我们正在面对什么
You have no idea what we're dealing with.
我知道 我见到...
I do. I saw where we're headed...
- 你给我闭嘴 我认真的 - 我他妈的见到了!
- shut up, man, seriously-- - I fucking saw it.
你告诉我你要为她而死
You're telling me you're gonna die for her.
但是我们都已经因为她而奄奄一息了
because we've all been dying for her.
你可以留在车里的
You can stay in the car, man.
妈?
Mom.
罗拉 你去那里了? 我联络不上你
Laura, where have you been? I can't reach you.
- 妈 你还好吗? - 罗拉 我见到些东西
- Mom, are you okay? - I'm seeing things, Laura.
- 我一直见到那个女孩 - 我很抱歉
- I keep seeing that girl. - I'm sorry.
- 是我的错 - 我们发生什么事了?
- It's my fault. - What's happening to us?
听我说 我不会让你发生任何事
Listen to me. I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
我要去想方法解决这件事 我要去想方法阻止它
I'm gonna sort this out somehow. I'm gonna stop this somehow.
妈?
Mom?
- 妈! 妈! - 我会保护你的
- Mom! Mom! - I'm gonna protect you.
妈
Mom!
妈!
Mom.
罗拉
Laura.
罗拉!
Laura!
泰勒
Tyler.
我真的很担心你啊
I was so worried about you.
嘿 罗拉
Laura, hey.
罗拉 看着我
Laura, look at me.
我妈 她...
My mom, she's..
天啊
Jesus.
你发生什么事了?
What happened to you?
嗨
Hi.
你想要什么?
What do you want from me?
你究竟还想要什么?
What else do you want from me?
罗拉 我只是想跟你做朋友
I just wanna be friends, Laura.
好朋友
best friends.
永远的好朋友
Forever.
罗拉
Laura.
来我这里
come to me.
Translate by Lavigkaye
翻译: Lavigkaye
罗拉·伍德森分享了一段影片
周五晚狂欢
好友请求
确认
嬴得一次豪华房车之旅
罗拉·伍德森
好友数目
嘿 晚点酒吧见?
今天我爸爸达入五十五岁 生日快乐 我很想念你 爸爸
可以去参观野生动物护理中心
和这些非凡的小孩一起玩 感谢 #给小孩的希望
罗拉·伍德森出席了一个由给小孩的希望举行的活动
整学期都在我叔叔的地方住
泰勒·麦考密克
罗拉·伍德森
美好的一天
古斯塔沃·加西亚: 你们两个是在约会吗?
奥利维亚·马西森: 他就想
DSM 精神疾病诊断与统计手册
The Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders
由美国精神医学学会出版
是一本在美国与其他国家最常使用来诊断精神疾病的指导手册
我们什么时候再一起去玩?
不如今晚?
玛·丽娜向你传送了一个好友请求
你好 罗拉
我是精神科堂的玛丽娜
希望我们可以交个朋友
玛·丽娜向你传送了一个好友请求
你好 罗拉
我是精神科堂的玛丽娜
希望我们可以交个朋友
又在我的梦中出现
玛·丽娜新增了一段影片在我的动画中
玛·丽娜新增了一张相片在避难所中
我们毁灭我们所不认识的
玛·丽娜新增了一段影片在我的动画中
玛·丽娜新增了一张相片在我的作品中
艺术家总是孤单的
为什么这个梦这么真实?
玛·丽娜新增了一段影片在我的动画中
玛·丽娜新增了一张相片在我的作品中
我昨晚的梦
过去总是缠绕着我
你现在是罗拉·伍德森的朋友了
查看个人档案
罗拉·伍德森
玛·丽娜和罗拉·伍德森
罗拉:
真是太惊人了! 我不能相信你竟然一个人自己做出那些动画来
玛·丽娜:
多谢你 我刚刚发表了一个新的 希望你不介意我标签了你
其实这比人们想象中更容易 对了 你知道吗 因为计算机都有灵魂的
我的意思是我们的灵魂 因为我们将一切都分享上网 你同意吗?
嘿 你还在吗? 如果在忙就算了 不用在意
对了 我们可不可以约出来一起喝杯咖啡
我知道一个很好的地方 我经常都会去那里
你认为如何 不如明天? 或者后天? 随便了
另一张上周拍的照片
奥利维亚·马西森和高比还有古斯塔沃·加西亚
嘿! 明天是你的生日呢!
你会举行个派对吗?
我真的很期待呢!
你还在吗?
嘿! 明天是你的生日呢!
你会举行个派对吗?
我真的很期待呢!
嘿! 明天是你的生日呢!
你会举行个派对吗?
我真的很期待呢!
你还在吗?
玛·丽娜新增了一张相片在避难所中
玛·丽娜新增了一段影片在我的动画中
我们毁灭我们所不认识的
玛·丽娜新增了一张相片在我的作品中
艺术家总是孤单的
为什么这个梦这么真实?
正在载入更旧的贴文
视像通话要求
玛丽娜·米尔斯
罗拉·伍德森被标签在一张相片中
和奥利维亚·马西森
视像通话要求
玛丽娜·米尔斯
请听电话吧 我很抱歉
我没有心发脾气的 请致电给我
我只是想知道你为什么说你只和泰勒一起
我不明白 我做了什么?
说点什么啊
我做错了什么?
我想将礼物送给你 我真的花了两个星期去做
我从我们第一次见面就开始准备了
请 请你原谅我 我们应该要当好朋友的
我们有很多的事要去做 我会为你做任何事
罗拉 你与我注定要在一起的 我们就像一对姊妹 你要给我一次机会
我内心真的很痛苦 我要做什么来补偿你?
对不起 对不起 罗拉 我真的很想跟你说 致电给我
你是我生命中唯一重要的事 我不能失去你 我现在要打给你
没有你 我只有孤独 我不能够再次孤独了
罗拉 你在吗?
我想将礼物送给你 我真的花了两个星期去做
我从我们第一次见面就开始准备了
请 请你原谅我 我们应该要当好朋友的
我们有很多的事要去做 我会为你做任何事
罗拉 你与我注定要在一起的 我们就像一对姊妹 你要给我一次机会
我内心真的很痛苦 我要做什么来补偿你?
对不起 对不起 罗拉 我真的很想跟你说 致电给我
你是我生命中唯一重要的事 我不能失去你 我现在要打给你
没有你 我只有孤独 我不能够再次孤独了
罗拉 你在吗?
取消好友关系
你确定要和玛丽娜取消好友关系吗?
确认
玛丽娜向你传来讯息
玛丽娜传了一段影片给你
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
删除影片
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
删除影片
泰勒·麦考密克向你传来讯息
你为什么要发布它?
罗拉·伍德森发布了一段影片
和玛丽娜·米尔斯 高比 古斯塔沃·加西亚 还有833位其他人
删除影片
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
为什么你要发布这东西?
你被黑客入侵了?
不能相信你又发了这东西!
提提你 你会被停课的
我见到你推开她 做得好
这是跟你打的那个女生?
你确定要和玛丽娜取消好友关系吗?
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
玛丽娜现在跟古斯塔沃·加西亚是朋友了
古斯塔沃·加西亚
(纪念专页)
在爱的回忆中安息
高比向你传来讯息
老友 尽快去看看你的主页
罗拉·伍德森发布了一段影片
和古斯塔沃·加西亚 高比 奥利维亚·马西森 还有609位其他人
删除影片
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
删除影片
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
我发誓这些都不是我发布的
我的账号不受我的控制
你将会知道孤独的感觉
你太呕心了!
首先你发布了自杀影片 然后是这个?
我还以为你是他的朋友
你太呕心了!
首先你发布了自杀影片 然后是这个?
我还以为你是他的朋友
说真的 你是谁
首先你发布了自杀影片 然后是这个?
我还以为你是他的朋友
说真的 你是谁
快删除你的账号!
我还以为你是他的朋友
说真的 你是谁
快删除你的账号!
快停止了! 我要去告发你了!
说真的 你是谁
快删除你的账号!
快停止了! 我要去告发你了!
如果你不会控制你的账号就快把它删除吧!
玛丽娜现在跟古斯塔沃·加西亚是朋友了
纪念
黑镜
黑镜魔法
嘿 各位 罗拉没有发布这些东西 你们认识罗拉的
她是绝对不会这样...
发现两具面部残缺不全的男童尸体
当地警方在周日晚上发现了一件可怕的案件
他们发现两具十二岁的男童尸体
发现面部残缺不全的男童尸体
伊茨小姐现在跟玛丽娜是朋友了
罗拉·伍德森发布了一段影片
和伊茨小姐 还有208位其他人
说真的 你有病 快去看医生吧
患上癌症吧 婊子!
为什么你身边的人都在死亡?
希望你就是下一个 我不想再从你主页上看到这些呕心的贴文
罗拉 你真够朋友
你确认要删除你的账号吗
删除账号
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
你确认要删除你的账号吗
删除账号
泰勒·麦考密克
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
高比
你确认要删除你的账号吗
删除账号
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
取消和罗拉·伍德森的好友关系
你确定要和罗拉·伍德森取消好友关系吗?
未知的错误
发生未知的错误 请你稍后再尝试
管理人办公室
病人记录
玛丽娜·妮蒂法
精神状态不正常
反应型依恋障碍
拔毛癖
Moore's Grove农舍发生火灾
一名生还者在重症监护中
邻居: 公社是一个邪教
奥利维亚·马西森现在跟玛丽娜是朋友了
禁止进入
入侵者将会被射击
你现在跟玛丽娜是朋友了
卡罗琳·伍德森要求视像通话
罗·拉
艾莉西亚?戴南?卡瑞
取消和玛?丽娜的好友关系
就读 塞勒姆大学
居住 塞勒姆 麻萨诸塞州
塞勒姆
一个在历史和传闻上
发生很多关于巫师 巫术等奇怪事件的地方
黑镜仪式
通常用作诅咒或者召唤恶魔
黑镜社团
执行这个仪式的最好方法是设一个小祭坛来进行所有的魔法仪式
黑镜邪教
本地大屋出售给神秘组织 被控施展巫术
我透过后门找到些邪教记录档案 找到了一个原始的石板画
罗拉 你有病吗?
绝交 婊子!
太呕心了! 你不配当伊茨的朋友!
母亲名字: 埃达·妮蒂法
消防队员在周日晚赶到Moore's Grove的火灾现场
但为时已晚 大火已经夺去了多条人命...
本地大屋出售给神秘组织 被控施展巫术
特别新闻
Moore's Grove发生致命大火
一名生还者在重症监护中